A Guide to the Rockefeller Family and Associates (Room 5600), General Files, 1987-1991, RG 39 FA1505
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Rockefeller Family and Associates (Room 5600), General Files, 1987-1991; 39; 234.9 Cubic Feet 597 containers
  - International Relations, 1987-1991; 15; 27.34 Cubic Feet 72 letter document boxes
    - Countries/Continents, 2
      - Germany (Box 306, Folder 4)
      - Greece - A-Z (Box 306, Folder 5)
      - Guinea - A-Z (Box 306, Folder 6)
      - India - A-Z (Box 306, Folder 7)
      - Iran (Box 306, Folder 8)
      - Ireland (Box 307, Folder 1)
      - Israel - A-Z (Box 307, Folder 2)
      - Israel - Cousins (Box 313, Folder 3)
      - Israel - Jerusalem Foundation (Box 307, Folder 3)
      - Italy - A-Z (Box 307, Folder 4)
      - Italy - Philip Mazzei Association (Box 307, Folder 5)
      - Japan - A-I (Box 307, Folder 6)
      - Japan - J-Z (Box 308, Folder 1-2)
      - Japan - Japan Center for International Exchange (Box 308, Folder 3-4)
      - Japan - Japan Society (Box 308, Folder 5)
      - Japan - Japan Society - Contributions (Box 309, Folder 1)
      - Japan - Japan Society - Contributions - Cousins (Box 313, Folder 4)
      - Japan - Japan Foundation (Box 309, Folder 2)
      - Kenya (Box 309, Folder 3)
      - Mexico - A-Z (Box 309, Folder 4)
      - Mexico - A-Z - Cousins (Box 313, Folder 5)
      - Middle East (Box 310, Folder 1)
      - Middle East - Cousins (Box 313, Folder 6)
      - Pakistan - A-Z (Box 310, Folder 2)
      - Peru - A-Z (Box 310, Folder 3)
      - Philippines - A-Z (Box 310, Folder 4)
      - Poland - A-Z (Box 310, Folder 5)
      - Portugal - A-Z (Box 310, Folder 6)
      - Romania (Box 310, Folder 7)
      - South Africa - A-Z (Box 311, Folder 1)
      - South Africa - A-Z - Cousins (Box 313, Folder 7)
      - Spain - A-Z (Box 311, Folder 2)
      - Thailand (Box 311, Folder 3)
      - Thailand - Thai-American Friendship Committee (Box 311, Folder 4)
      - USSR - A-I (Box 311, Folder 5)
      - USSR - I-Z (Box 312, Folder 1)
      - USSR - A-Z - Cousins (Box 313, Folder 8)
      - USSR - Center for U.S.-U.S.S.R. Initiatives (Box 313, Folder 9)
      - USSR - Commission on U.S.-Soviet Relations (Box 313, Folder 10)
      - USSR - The Entertainment Summit (Box 312, Folder 5)
      - USSR - Entertainment Summit - Cousins (Box 313, Folder 11)
      - USSR - Informal US-Soviet Conference (Dartmouth Conference) (Box 312, Folder 2-4)
    - Foreign Aid, 3
      - Foreign Aid - A-Z (Box 314, Folder 1)
      - Foreign Aid - A-Z - Cousins and Fifth Generation (Box 313, Folder 12-13)
      - Care (Box 314, Folder 2)
      - Citizens Network for Foreign Affairs, 1987-1991 (Box 314, Folder 3-4)
      - Citizens Network for Economic and Security Assistance, 1986 (Box 314, Folder 5)
      - Hunger Project (Box 314, Folder 6)
      - Hunger Project - Cousins (Box 315, Folder 1)
      - International Center for Development Policy (Box 315, Folder 2-3)
      - Neighbor to Neighbor (Action Fund) (Box 315, Folder 4, Box 317, Folder 1)
      - Overseas Development Council (Box 316, Folder 1)
      - Overseas Development Council - Cousins (Box 317, Folder 2)
      - Resources Development Foundation (Box 316, Folder 2-3)
      - Synergos Institute (Box 318, Folder 1)
      - Synergos Institute - Cousins (Box 317, Folder 3)
    - Foreign Policy, 4
      - Foreign Policy - A-Z (Box 316, Folder 4)
      - Foreign Policy - A-Z - Cousins (Box 317, Folder 4)
      - Committee for National Security - Cousins (Box 317, Folder 5, Box 328, Folder 1)
      - Council on Foreign Relations (Box 318, Folder 2)
      - Council on Foreign Relations - Contributions (Box 318, Folder 3)
      - Council on Foreign Relations - Contributions - Cousins (Box 328, Folder 2)
      - Council on Foreign Relations - Fundraising (Box 318, Folder 4)
      - Council on Foreign Relations - Middle East Trip, 1990 February (Box 318, Folder 5)
      - Council on Foreign Relations - Southern Africa Study Group (Box 319, Folder 1-3)
      - Council on Foreign Relations - USSR Trip (Box 319, Folder 4)
      - Foreign Policy Association (Box 320, Folder 1-2)
      - National Committee on American Foreign Policy (Box 320, Folder 3)
    - Pan American, 5
      - Pan American - A-C (Box 320, Folder 4)
      - Pan American - D-Z (Box 321, Folder 1-2)
      - Pan American - A-Z - Cousins and Fifth Generation (Box 328, Folder 3-7)
      - Americas Society - A-L (Box 321, Folder 3-4)
      - Americas Society - M-Z (Box 322, Folder 1-2)
      - Americas Society - General Correspondence, 1990 (Box 322, Folder 3)
      - Americas Society - Canadian Affairs, 1988-1991 (Box 322, Folder 4-5)
      - Americas Society - Canadian Affairs Program, 1987 (Box 323, Folder 1)
      - Americas Society - Chairman's International Advisory Council - A-Z (Box 323, Folder 2)
      - Americas Society - Contributions (Box 323, Folder 3)
      - Americas Society - Fundraising (Box 323, Folder 4)
      - Americas Society - Fundraising, 1990 January 1 (Box 323, Folder 5)
      - Americas Society - Fundraising Spring Party, 1991 (Box 323, Folder 6)
      - Americas Society - Fundraising Spring Party, 1989 June 6 (Box 324, Folder 1)
      - Americas Society - Fundraising Spring Party, 1988 June 9 (Box 324, Folder 2)
      - Americas Society - Growth Study, 1985-1986 (Box 325, Folder 1)
      - Americas Society - Growth Study Distribution, 1986-1987 (Box 325, Folder 2)
      - Americas Society - Meetings (Box 325, Folder 3)
      - Americas Society - Membership, 1984-1987 (Box 325, Folder 4)
      - Americas Society - Trips - Canada, 1990 May 31-June 1 (Box 326, Folder 1)
      - Americas Society - Trips - Ecuador, 1987 February (Box 326, Folder 2)
      - Americas Society - Caribbean Central American Action - A-Z (Box 326, Folder 3)
      - Americas Society - Caribbean Central American Action - Meetings (Box 326, Folder 4-5)
      - Americas Society - Center for Inter-American Affairs - A-Z (Box 327, Folder 1)
      - Americas Society - Council of the Americas (Box 327, Folder 2)
      - Americas Society - Consortium for Inter-American Trade and Development (Box 327, Folder 3)
      - Americas Society - Pan American Society - A-Z (Box 327, Folder 4)
    - Peace, 6
      - Peace - C (Box 327, Folder 5)
      - Peace - D-S (Box 327, Folder 6)
      - Peace - T-Z (Box 329, Folder 1-2)
      - Peace - A-B - Cousins and Fifth Generation (Box 328, Folder 8)
      - Peace - C - Cousins and Fifth Generation (Box 317, Folder 6-7)
      - Peace - D-S - Cousins (Box 331, Folder 1-4)
      - Peace - T-W - Cousins (Box 332, Folder 1-3)
      - Access: A Security Information Service (Box 332, Folder 4)
      - Architects-Designers-Planners for Social Responsibility (Box 333, Folder 1)
      - Better World Society (Box 329, Folder 3)
      - Better World Society - Cousins (Box 333, Folder 2)
      - Bilderberg Meetings (Box 329, Folder 4)
      - Business Executives for National Security Education Fund, Inc. (Box 329, Folder 5)
      - Business Executives for National Security Education Fund, Inc. - Printer Matter (Box 330, Folder 1)
      - Business Executives for National Security Education Fund, Inc. - Cousins (Box 333, Folder 3, Box 334, Folder 1)
      - Campaign for Peace and Democracy/East and West (Box 334, Folder 2)
      - Center for Economic Conversion (Box 334, Folder 3)
      - Center for Education on Nuclear War, Inc. (Box 334, Folder 4)
      - Center for Innovative Diplomacy (Box 335, Folder 1-2, Box 336, Folder 1)
      - Center for Psychological Studies in the Nuclear Age (Box 336, Folder 2)
      - Citizen Alert (Box 337, Folder 1)
      - Citizen Exchange Council (Box 330, Folder 2)
      - Citizen Exchange Council - Cousins (Box 337, Folder 2)
      - Communications Consortium (Box 334, Folder 5, Box 338, Folder 1)
      - Council for a Livable World Education Fund (Box 335, Folder 3, Box 338, Folder 2-3)
      - Downwinders (Box 339, Folder 1-2)
      - Educators for Social Responsibility (Box 339, Folder 3, Box 340, Folder 1)
      - The Forum Foundation (The Forum Institute) (Box 339, Folder 4)
      - Foundation for the Arts of Peace (Box 336, Folder 3)
      - Foundation for International Security (Box 340, Folder 2)
      - Global Outlook Education Institute (Box 340, Folder 3)
      - Dana McLean Greeley Foundation for Peace and Justice, Inc. (Box 341, Folder 1)
      - Institute for Peace and International Security (Box 341, Folder 2-3)
      - Interamerican Research Center (Box 341, Folder 4)
      - International Peace Academy (Box 330, Folder 3)
      - International Peace Academy - Cousins (Box 340, Folder 4)
      - International Physicians for the Prevention of Nuclear War, Inc. (Box 330, Folder 4)
      - International Physicians for the Prevention of Nuclear War, Inc. - Cousins (Box 342, Folder 1)
      - Jobs With Peace, Inc. and Jobs with Peace Education Fund, Inc. (Box 342, Folder 2-3)
      - Lawyers Alliance for Nuclear Arms Control, Inc. (Box 343, Folder 1)
      - National Campaign to Save the ABM Treaty (Box 343, Folder 2-3)
      - National Commission for Economic Conversion and Disarmament (Box 343, Folder 4)
      - Nuclear Times, Inc. (Box 343, Folder 5)
      - Nuclear Control Institute (Box 344, Folder 1)
      - Options (Box 344, Folder 2)
      - Parliamentarians Global Action (Box 344, Folder 3)
      - Peace Child Foundation (Box 345, Folder 1)
      - Peace and Common Security (Box 345, Folder 2)
      - Peace Development Fund (Box 345, Folder 3, Box 347, Folder 1)
      - Peace Links (Box 347, Folder 3)
      - The Peace Through Law Education Fund (Box 346, Folder 1)
      - The Peace Through Law Education Fund - Cousins (Box 347, Folder 2)
      - Ploughshares Fund (Box 346, Folder 2)
      - Ploughshares Fund - Cousins (Box 348, Folder 1)
      - Richard Pollock Associates (Box 347, Folder 4)
      - Sadat Peace Foundation (Box 346, Folder 5)
      - Sadat Peace Foundation - Cousins (Box 348, Folder 2)
      - Safer World, Inc. (Box 348, Folder 3)
      - Sane (Box 349, Folder 1)
      - Sane Education Fund of Pennsylvania (Box 349, Folder 2)
      - Sane-Freeze Education Fund (Box 349, Folder 3)
      - Search for Common Ground (Box 346, Folder 3)
      - Search for Common Ground - Cousins (Box 349, Folder 4)
      - Up With People (Box 346, Folder 4)
      - Washington Council on Non-Proliferation (Box 350, Folder 1)
      - Wisconsin Project on Nuclear Arms Control (Box 350, Folder 2)
      - Women for a Meaningful Summit (Box 350, Folder 3)
      - Women's Action for Nuclear Disarmament Education Fund, Inc. (Box 350, Folder 4)
      - World Policy Institute (Box 351, Folder 1-2)
    - United Nations, 7
      - United Nations (Box 346, Folder 6)
      - United Nations - A-M (Box 346, Folder 7)
      - United Nations - N-Z (Box 352, Folder 1)
      - United Nations - N-Z - Cousins (Box 358, Folder 1)
      - Business Council for the United Nations (Box 352, Folder 2)
      - Friends of the United Nations (Box 351, Folder 3)
      - United Nations Association of the United States of America (Box 352, Folder 3)
      - International Children's Emergency Fund (UNICEF) (Box 352, Folder 4)
      - United Nations International Children's Fund (UNICEF) - Cousins (Box 358, Folder 2)
      - United Nations Development Fund for Women (UNIFEM) (Box 352, Folder 5)
      - United Nations Development Program (UNDP) (Box 352, Folder 6)
      - United Nations Environment Programme (Box 352, Folder 7)
      - University of Peace (Box 353, Folder 1)
    - United States Government, 8
      - Agency for International Development (AID) - International Executive Service Corps (IESC) (Box 353, Folder 2)
      - Executive Council on Foreign Diplomats (Box 353, Folder 3)
      - Department of State - A-Z (Box 353, Folder 4)
      - Department of State - Fine Arts Committee (Box 353, Folder 5)
      - Department of State - Friends of Art and Preservation in Embassies (Box 354, Folder 1)
  - J-M, 1987-1991; 16; 0.38 Cubic Feet 1 letter document box
    - J - Miscellaneous (Box 354, Folder 2)
    - K - Miscellaneous (Box 354, Folder 3)
    - K - Miscellaneous - Katzenback, L. Emery & Mrs. Shirley Steinman (Box 354, Folder 4)
    - L - Miscellaneous (Box 354, Folder 5)
    - M - Miscellaneous (Box 354, Folder 6)
  - Medicine, 1987-1991; 17; 14.81 Cubic Feet 39 letter document boxes
    - Medicine - A-Z, 1
      - Medicine - A (Box 354, Folder 7)
      - Medicine - B-G (Box 355, Folder 1-4)
      - Medicine - H-O (Box 356, Folder 1-4)
      - Medicine - P-Z (Box 357, Folder 1-3)
      - Medicine - A-Z - Cousins (Box 358, Folder 3-13)
      - Alzheimer's Disease and Related Disorders Association (Box 359, Folder 1)
      - Alzheimer's Disease and Related Disorders Association - Cousins (Box 358, Folder 14)
      - American Association of Ayurvedic Medicine (Box 359, Folder 2-3)
      - American Cancer Society (Box 360, Folder 1-2)
      - American Cancer Society - Cousins (Box 358, Folder 15)
      - American Foundation for AIDS Research (Box 360, Folder 3)
      - American Foundation for AIDS Research - Cousins and Fifth Generation (Box 358, Folder 16-17)
      - American Heath Foundation (Box 360, Folder 4)
      - Amigos de las Americas (Box 361, Folder 1)
      - Arthritis Foundation, Inc. (Box 361, Folder 2)
      - Botanical Dimensions (Box 361, Folder 3)
      - Cancer Care, Inc. (Box 361, Folder 4)
      - Cancer Research Institute (Box 361, Folder 5)
      - Cancer Research Institute, Inc. - Cousins (Box 358, Folder 18)
      - Deafness Research Foundation (Box 361, Folder 6)
      - Doctors Without Borders USA, Inc. (Box 362, Folder 1)
      - Fetzer Institute (Box 362, Folder 2)
      - General Motors Cancer Research Foundation (Box 362, Folder 3)
      - House Ear Institute (Box 362, Folder 4)
      - Institute for the Advancement of Health (Box 362, Folder 5, Box 363, Folder 1-2)
      - Institute for the Advancement of Health - Cousins (Box 373, Folder 1)
      - Institute for Holistic Blood Diagnosis (Box 363, Folder 3)
      - Institute for Humanistic Science (Box 363, Folder 4)
      - Juvenile Diabetes Foundation (Box 364, Folder 1-2)
      - Harvard Medical School (Box 364, Folder 3)
      - Lancaster Foundation (Box 364, Folder 4)
      - Maharishi-Ayurveda Association of America and Health Center (Box 364, Folder 5, Box 365, Folder 1)
      - The Robert Mapplethorpe Laboratory for Aids Research (Box 365, Folder 2)
      - Medical Illness Counseling Center (Box 365, Folder 3)
      - Medical Illness Counseling Center - Cousins (Box 373, Folder 2)
      - Mind-Body Medical Institute (Box 365, Folder 4)
      - Mind-Body Medical Institute - Cousins (Box 373, Folder 3)
      - National Council on Alcoholism and Drug Dependence (Box 366, Folder 1-2)
      - National Foundation for Cancer Research (Box 366, Folder 3)
      - National Foundation for Facial Reconstruction (Box 366, Folder 4)
      - National Organization for Circumcision Information Resource Centers (Box 366, Folder 5)
      - National Multiple Sclerosis Society (Box 366, Folder 6)
      - New York Academy of Medicine (Box 366, Folder 7)
      - New York Blood Center (Box 367, Folder 1)
      - Open Door Family Health Centers (Box 367, Folder 2)
      - Oubre, Alondra Yvette (Box 367, Folder 3)
      - Physicians for Social Responsibility (Box 367, Folder 4)
      - Physicians for Social Responsibility - Cousins (Box 373, Folder 4)
      - The Skin Cancer Foundation (Box 367, Folder 5)
      - United Cerebral Palsy Association, Inc. (Box 367, Folder 6)
      - Ann Wigmore Foundation (Box 368, Folder 1-2)
    - Alcoholism, 2
      - Alcoholism - A-Z (Box 367, Folder 3)
      - Alcoholism Council of Greater New York (Box 369, Folder 1)
      - Children of Alcoholics Foundation, Inc. (Box 369, Folder 2-3)
      - Freedom Institute (Box 369, Folder 4)
      - National Council of Alcoholism (Box 369, Folder 5, Box 370, Folder 1)
      - National Council of Alcoholism - Fundraising (Box 370, Folder 2)
      - The Weekend Center (Box 370, Folder 3)
    - Hospitals, 3
      - Hospitals - A-D (Box 370, Folder 4-5)
      - Hospitals - E-Z (Box 371, Folder 1-4)
      - Hospitals - A-Z - Cousins and Fifth Generation (Box 373, Folder 5-11)
      - Charing Cross Westminster Medical College (Box 371, Folder 5)
      - Columbia-Presbyterian Medical Center, NY, NY (Box 372, Folder 1-2)
      - Dartmouth-Hitchcock Medical Center (Box 372, Folder 3)
      - Eisenhower Medical Center (Box 372, Folder 4)
      - Harlem Hospital Center (Box 374, Folder 1)
      - Hospital for Special Surgery (Box 374, Folder 2)
      - Memorial Sloan Kettering Cancer Center (MSKCC) - A-M (Box 374, Folder 3-4)
      - Memorial Sloan Kettering Cancer Center (MSKCC) - N-Z (Box 375, Folder 1)
      - Memorial Sloan Kettering Cancer Center (MSKCC) - Annual Reports (Box 375, Folder 2)
      - Memorial Sloan Kettering Cancer Center (MSKCC) - Board of Overseers, Board of Managers (Box 375, Folder 3, Box 376, Folder 1)
      - Memorial Sloan Kettering Cancer Center (MSKCC) - Center for Diagnostic Imaging and Breast Cancer (Box 376, Folder 2)
      - Memorial Sloan Kettering Cancer Center (MSKCC) - Contributions (Box 376, Folder 3-4)
      - Memorial Sloan Kettering Cancer Center (MSKCC) - Contributions - Cousins and Fifth Generation (Box 373, Folder 12-13)
      - Memorial Sloan Kettering Cancer Center (MSKCC) - Contributions JY Ranch, 1978-1991 (Box 376, Folder 5)
      - Memorial Sloan Kettering Cancer Center (MSKCC) - Convocation (Box 376, Folder 6)
      - Memorial Sloan Kettering Cancer Center (MSKCC) - Finances (Box 377, Folder 1)
      - Memorial Sloan Kettering Cancer Center (MSKCC) - Finances - Joint Audit Committee (Box 377, Folder 2)
      - Memorial Sloan Kettering Cancer Center (MSKCC) - Finances - Joint Finance and Funding Committee, 1987 (Box 377, Folder 3)
      - Memorial Sloan Kettering Cancer Center (MSKCC) - Fundraising - General (Box 377, Folder 4, Box 378, Folder 1-2)
      - Memorial Sloan Kettering Cancer Center (MSKCC) - Fundraising - A-M (Box 378, Folder 3-5)
      - Memorial Sloan Kettering Cancer Center (MSKCC) - Fundraising - N-Z (Box 379, Folder 1)
      - Memorial Sloan Kettering Cancer Center (MSKCC) - Fundraising - Japan (Box 379, Folder 2)
      - Memorial Sloan Kettering Cancer Center (MSKCC) - Fundraising - Kluge, John (Box 379, Folder 3)
      - Memorial Sloan Kettering Cancer Center (MSKCC) - Fundraising - Sinatra VII (Box 380, Folder 1)
      - Memorial Sloan Kettering Cancer Center (MSKCC) - Galbraith, Mrs. Evan G. Jr. (Box 380, Folder 2)
      - Memorial Sloan Kettering Cancer Center (MSKCC) - Enid A. Haupt Pavilion (Box 380, Folder 3)
      - Memorial Sloan Kettering Cancer Center (MSKCC) - Joint Nominating Committee (Box 380, Folder 4)
      - Memorial Sloan Kettering Cancer Center (MSKCC) - Meetings (Box 380, Folder 5)
      - Memorial Sloan Kettering Cancer Center (MSKCC) - Meetings - Board of Managers 1991 (Box 380, Folder 6)
      - Memorial Sloan Kettering Cancer Center (MSKCC) - Meetings - Board of Managers 1989, 1989 September 27; May 24 1989 (Box 381, Folder 1-2)
      - Memorial Sloan Kettering Cancer Center (MSKCC) - Meetings - Board of Managers 1989, 1989 January 25 (Box 381, Folder 3)
      - Memorial Sloan Kettering Cancer Center (MSKCC) - Meetings - Board of Managers 1988, 1988 January 27 (Box 381, Folder 4)
      - Memorial Sloan Kettering Cancer Center (MSKCC) - Meetings - Board of Managers 1988, 1988 May 25 (Box 382, Folder 1)
      - Memorial Sloan Kettering Cancer Center (MSKCC) - Meetings - Board of Overseers 1989, 1989 July 26 (Box 382, Folder 2)
      - Memorial Sloan Kettering Cancer Center (MSKCC) - Meetings - Board of Overseers, Board of Managers 1987, 1987 March 25 (Box 382, Folder 3)
      - Memorial Sloan Kettering Cancer Center (MSKCC) - Meetings - Board of Overseers, Board of Managers 1987, 1987 July 22 (Box 382, Folder 4)
      - Memorial Sloan Kettering Cancer Center (MSKCC) - Meetings - Executive Committee (Box 383, Folder 1)
      - Memorial Sloan Kettering Cancer Center (MSKCC) - Meetings - Institutional Policy Committee, 1990-1991 (Box 383, Folder 2-3)
      - Memorial Sloan Kettering Cancer Center (MSKCC) - Meetings - Institutional Policy Committee, 1987-1989 (Box 383, Folder 4-6)
      - Memorial Sloan Kettering Cancer Center (MSKCC) - Meetings - Institutional Policy Committee and Long-Range Planning Subcommittee, 1988 (Box 384, Folder 1)
      - Memorial Sloan Kettering Cancer Center (MSKCC) - Meetings - Long-Range Planning Subcommittee of the Institutional Policy Committee, 1987 (Box 384, Folder 2)
      - Memorial Sloan Kettering Cancer Center (MSKCC) - Meetings - Joint Organizational Policy Committee, 1987-1989 (Box 384, Folder 3-5)
      - Memorial Sloan Kettering Cancer Center (MSKCC) - Presidents Council (Box 385, Folder 1)
      - Memorial Sloan Kettering Cancer Center (MSKCC) - Printed Matter (Box 385, Folder 2)
      - Memorial Sloan Kettering Cancer Center (MSKCC) - Rockefeller Research Laboratories (Box 385, Folder 3)
      - Memorial Sloan Kettering Cancer Center (MSKCC) - Rockefeller Research Laboratories - A-Z (Box 385, Folder 4)
      - Memorial Sloan Kettering Cancer Center (MSKCC) - Rockefeller Research Laboratories - Dedication (Box 386, Folder 1)
      - Memorial Sloan Kettering Cancer Center (MSKCC) - Rockefeller Research Laboratories - Laurance S. Rockefeller Board Room (Box 386, Folder 2)
      - Memorial Sloan Kettering Cancer Center (MSKCC) - Rockefeller Research Laboratories - Laurance S. Rockefeller Board Room - Fundraising (Box 386, Folder 3)
      - Memorial Sloan Kettering Cancer Center (MSKCC) - Memorial Hospital for Cancer and Allied Diseases (Box 387, Folder 1)
      - Memorial Sloan Kettering Cancer Center (MSKCC) - S.K.I. Realty (Box 387, Folder 2)
      - Memorial Sloan Kettering Cancer Center (MSKCC) - Sloan-Kettering Institute (Box 387, Folder 3)
      - Memorial Sloan Kettering Cancer Center (MSKCC) - Society of Memorial Sloan-Kettering Cancer Center (Box 387, Folder 4)
      - Memorial Sloan Kettering Cancer Center (MSKCC) - Society of Memorial Sloan-Kettering Cancer Center - A-Z (Box 387, Folder 5)
      - Memorial Sloan Kettering Cancer Center (MSKCC) - Society of Memorial Sloan-Kettering Cancer Center - Contributions (Box 387, Folder 6)
      - Montefiore Medical Center (Box 388, Folder 1)
      - Phelps Memorial Hospital Center (Box 388, Folder 2)
      - Phelps Memorial Hospital - Cousins (Box 373, Folder 14)
      - St. John's Hospital, Jackson, Wyoming (Box 388, Folder 3)
      - Society of New York Hospital - New York Hospital-Cornell Medical Center (Box 388, Folder 4, Box 389, Folder 1)
      - Society of New York Hospital - New York Hospital-Cornell Medical Center - Contributions (Box 389, Folder 2)
      - Society of New York Hospital - New York Hospital-Cornell Medical Center - Printed Matter (Box 389, Folder 3)
      - United Hospital Fund of New York (Box 390, Folder 1)
    - Mental Health, 4
      - Mental Health - A-Z (Box 390, Folder 2-5)
      - Mental Health - A-Z - Cousins (Box 373, Folder 15-16)
      - C.G. Jung Institute of Los Angeles (Box 390, Folder 6, Box 391, Folder 1)
      - C.G. Jung institute of San Francisco (Box 391, Folder 2-3)
      - The Lifwynn Foundation (Box 391, Folder 4)
      - Recoveries Anonymous (Box 391, Folder 5)
    - Narcotics, 5
      - Narcotics - A-Z (Box 392, Folder 1)
      - Narcotics - A-Z - Cousins (Box 373, Folder 17)
      - Phoenix House (Box 392, Folder 2)
      - Phoenix House - Cousins (Box 373, Folder 18)
  - N-P, 1987-1991; 18; 0.38 Cubic Feet 1 letter document box
    - N - Miscellaneous (Box 392, Folder 3)
    - O - Miscellaneous (Box 392, Folder 4)
    - P - Miscellaneous (Box 392, Folder 5)
  - Philanthropy, 1987-1991; 19; 1.9 Cubic Feet 5 letter document boxes
    - Philanthropy - A-M (Box 392, Folder 6)